Okay, so it is time to stop the bubbling
effect. In order to do that, we do have
to access the event attribute. So come
into each of the logs and add the word
event because we're going to pass the
event into our function. Our function
needs to accept the event and then we're
just going to say e.
Stop
propagation.
And that stops propagation. Sorry,
really hard to spell that. Um, and then
we're going to console.log
hello.
So, if we come over to our running code
and we click uh the outer layer, oh,
it'd help if we have our console open.
If we click the outer layer, we get
hello. If we click the middle layer, we
get hello. And if we click the inner
layer, we get hello. So, now it's only
being called once because we've stopped
the bubbling from happening. And so that
is how you can prevent the bubbling from
happening. You access the event and you
say stop propagation and that will stop
it from going up the tree to any of the
higher components.